ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, AND EVENTS
IN THIS WORK ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL MINORS WERE FILMED IN COMPLIANCE
WITH STANDARD PRODUCTION GUIDELINES
KC BANK
1 WEEK BEOFRE D-DAY
This is really something.
Now let's see...
This is it.
You'll spot four faint holes.
I'll open it now.
The control room's main computer
will send a PIN command signal
to the main circuit board
in the vault.
Then the vault's main circuit board
generates a 16-digit PIN
and sends it back
to the control room's main computer.
Then the head of security
will come down here
and use that PIN to open the vault.
What?
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
That's really complicated.
- It is.
- Yes.
I'm in the control room's
main computer.
I also sent a PIN command
to the main circuit board.
Which chip did they say
produces the PIN?
Security program decoding...
PASSWORD DECRYPTOR
...complete.
Okay.
The PIN is 8-3-2-0-5-2-3
7-8-8-2-0-6-5-8-0.
Please.
Is it working?
Amazing.
D-day is one week away.
Before then, we must replace
the 500 billion won here
with 500 billion won worth
of our supernotes.
Okay, then.
Let's go!
- Let's do it.
- Go!
It's nice to see you, Madam Saimdang.
EPISODE 6:
D-DAY; THOSE WHO CHASE THE MONEY
BANK OF KOREA
D-DAY
Turn around.
BANK OF KOREA
KC BANK CONCLUDES
HISTORIC CASH TRANSPORT TODAY
It's KC Bank.
2.25 TRILLION WON CASH TRANSPORT
FOR NEW HEADQUARTERS RELOCATION
SINDAP RAILWAY BRIDGE, CHEONGGYECHEON
UNDER CONSTRUCTION
FIBER-OPTIC CABLE REPAIR IN PROGRESS
KC BANK SECURITY ROOM
Mr. Park.
Please have a coffee.
A coffee sounds nice.
Yun-gyu?
- Who are you?
- It is you, Park Yun-gyu.
Thanks.
Darn it.
I should really quit drinking.
WAITING ROOM
How much is left?
We still have
about 25 billion won down there.
We've been doing this
every night for a week
and we're not done yet.
I can't believe
we're doing this on the day of.
We have enough manpower here
to finish in an hour.
We've got this.
Let's go.
- Let's go,
- Okay.
Yes, Mr. Park.
Do you see that?
The PIN is 8-5-7-8-5-3-8
1-0-0-5-8-3-8-8-0.
- That piece of trash.
- Oh, yes.
- Tell them to pick it up.
- Yes, sir.
Hello, this is Security.
There's some trash in Area One.
Can you pick it up, please?
Hurry up.
Let's keep going.
I got nervous because Boss said
it was a big deal
but no one's standing guard.
What the fuck is going on?
Did everyone burrow underground?
Should we look around a bit more?
FIBER-OPTIC CABLE REPAIR IN PROGRESS
Hey, you...
Give me that.
Are you fucking
telling everyone who we are?
Put them away.
Hide your tools, punks.
Team One and I will go in.
Team Two, wait here.
Team Three, get the gas bomb, okay?
- Yes, Boss.
Just a moment, please.
- Mr. Park.
- Yes.
The NIS wants to speak
with our head of security.
- The NIS?
- Yes.
What for?
I don't know.
Take the call on line one.
Hello, this is the head of security.
Did the cash transport start?
No, not yet.
We'll start after lunch at 1 p.m.
What's the matter?
Halt all procedures until we arrive
and check the vault immediately.
Okay, understood.
There's nothing wrong.
- Yes?
- Let's go downstairs.
- Yes, sir.
- You keep watching.
What's this about?
Is this the last batch?
Yes, it's the last one.
Okay, let's go.
WAITING ROOM
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
What's going on?
I asked what's going on.
My partner said he has diarrhea.
He rushed inside.
Is that so?
Why are you drenched in sweat?
I tend to sweat a lot, you see.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
This is why
I didn't want to take the job.
All bank staff
think they're better than us.
Did I do something wrong?
All transport personnel
must wear a cap.
Don't you know that?
Oh, my bad.
I hung my cap on my belt
and forgot about it.
We changed the schedule around.
The kick-off time got delayed.
Rest in the waiting room.
Oh, yes, sir.
I'm real sorry about this.
I'll head to the waiting room then.
My bad. I'm sorry.
Gosh, I forgot the hat.
My goodness.
Darn it.
Why do those eyes seem familiar?
- Ready?
- Yes.
What's this about?
How much are you moving today?
It's 750 billion won
and our VIP safe-deposit boxes.
Where's the new headquarters?
It's close to Gangnam Station.
Wait!
What are you doing?
Load it fast!
Mole, where's your location?
Move it!
We're about 2km from the base camp.
It's all in the timing.
Once you reach the base camp,
start transporting, Kkangsooni.
How long do you need to hack
Seoul Central Traffic Control?
Around 20 minutes?
Gold Mine, when do you leave?
I don't know yet.
We'll set off after the search.
Okay.
The Mine's about to set off.
Mole, get into position quickly.
Let's go!
These three trucks
will each take 250 billion won.
The other truck will take
our VIP safe-deposit boxes.
Did you check everything?
There was nothing out of the ordinary
on security footage
and we confirmed
the vault was secure.
- Can I have a look?
- Sure.
Stop!
Boss.
We reached the base camp.
Kkangsooni, start transporting.
Fixer.
Stand by until we get word.
I'll see you on the top.
Come on, let's get moving.
Let's do this.
By the way.
Take this.
Why give me this?
Out of the bills
in each of these trucks
can you get me a 50,000-won bill?
Why?
We got a tip about counterfeit bills.
No way. That can't be.
What? You won't do it?
No.
I'll do it.
I should've noticed Han Soo-hyun
when she walked into the NIS.
We all got played.
Is there even 500 billion
in counterfeit bills?
Wait...
What's Han Soo-hyun up to?
She skipped lunch
and is sitting in a corner
of the night-duty room.
I'll grill her hard when I get back
- so make sure she's well fed.
- Yes, sir.
- You're not done yet?
- Don't pester me.
Rushing me won't help.
Tiger, report on the tunnel.
It's been 48 minutes
since around 20 Weasels
and Tiger entered the tunnel.
Hang on.
BUNKER A, BUNKER B, BUNKER C
There are there bunkers in total.
Where do we get in and out?
You're holding the map upside-down.
Jong-ro is this way.
Majang-dong is that way.
The bunker's right around the corner.
- Fuck you.
- Sorry, Boss.
Yes, I didn't serve
in the army, okay?
- Sorry, Boss.
- This bastard.
Sorry, Boss.
Fixer, set off in 16 minutes.
There's a place like this
30m underground?
This isn't the time to gape.
Not long from now
they'll come around that corner
with 500 billion won.
We'll use the gas bomb
while their guard is down
- take the 500 billion and leave.
- Okay.
What's wrong?
What's happening
when the power's still on?
Check the security footage
from other highways.
SAMIL-DAERO
It's nothing, is it?
SAMIL-DAERO, HANNAM-DAERO
Happy now?
Good job.
I'm doing this for Soo-hyun.
Promise to get her out.
Don't worry.
I told you, I made a deal.
Let's go.
Kkangsooni.
Estimated time to the top?
I expect to take about two minutes.
What the fuck?
ENTERING TUNNEL 1
Traffic lights, now.
What's wrong with the lights?
I can't control them remotely.
What's going on?
This is bad.
- Hello?
- I can't get through.
Yes, the roads are packed!
Do you want to die?
Fuck it.
Central Traffic Control detected it.
I'll lose control in a minute.
Kkangsooni, are you done yet?
- I'm almost done.
-I need you finished.
What's this?
This is it?
What the heck?
I'm so very sorry.
The traffic's at a standstill
and I fell asleep at the wheel.
You can't be like that on the road!
My bad.
My neck hurts so much.
This was meant to pay for materials.
I should see a doctor.
Oh, darn it.
Here.
It's five million won.
The money's clean.
Even a stray dog would take it.
It's cash.
I like your style.
- Thanks a lot!
- Sure.
Don't call your insurance.
- Drive safely.
- Thanks.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Take care. Go on your way.
I'm Iron Curtain, Kkangsooni.
There's nothing I can't do
if I fight with all my might.
- Okay.
- Darn it!
I don't believe this.
Fuck, run.
Come on.
Clean up.
Congratulations, Boss.
MOZART'S SYMPHONY NO. 25
We lost the 500 billion
to Jang Joong-hyuk.
What'll you do about Soo-hyun?
We lost the cash!
How will you get her out now?
That flash drive's worth that much?
I was going to
blackmail him with this...
to smuggle my way out.
What the heck is that anyway?
Who were you going to blackmail?
The NIS Director, of course.
The director of the NIS?
Print me an invoice
that'll get me
into Incheon Port container terminal.
Okay.
We've been stuck here for hours.
I'm as frustrated as this traffic.
I wonder whose fault that is.
Who's this?
I'm head of security
- at KC Bank's new headquarters.
- Oh, hello.
Did the trucks
reach their destination safely?
The cash is fine
but there's a problem
with the safe-deposit truck.
What is it?
Someone got into one of the boxes
belonging to
- Myeongseong's Chairman Bang.
- I'll be right there.
Take me to KC Bank's
new headquarters.
What's the matter?
Chairman Bang's safe
has been broken into.
What?
There you go.
My gosh.
That's a big one.
- Get it.
- All right.
Oh, gosh.
My word.
My goodness.
Hey.
You think it'll die, right?
How could it survive?
You're wrong.
It won't die.
It'll go on living in that state,
unable to die.
Listen.
Even when I'm eating a fish
I leave its internal organs intact.
That is how I deal with people...
and my stupid philosophy.
You know?
Fools who borrow my money
and don't pay me back.
I beat them just enough
so they don't die
and I let them go
once they pay principal and interest.
Then I wait
until their flesh grows back.
Okay.
Shouldn't we get moving now?
Darn it.
Where are you off to now?
Why?
You'll tag along?
Of course.
Hey.
Don't you get tired of tagging along
when you've got nothing to do?
Why are you complaining
when you're not at all in the right?
Have someone tail me
if you don't trust me.
- Chang-seok!
- Yes?
- You're with me.
- Me?
Yes, you.
Chang-seok.
Go, hurry on after him.
- Call me.
- Okay.
Did you call Gangnam Police?
They can't reach him.
Jang Joong-hyuk, that punk...
We can't reach him,
my safe has been broken into?
I can't let that get out.
Sir, someone
from the NIS Financial Crime Team
is here to see you.
I meant to call the police.
The NIS sent someone right away.
You got a tip-off, didn't you?
Yes.
How's your director doing?
We haven't talked since
our golf outing three weeks ago.
I'm sure he'll be fine
without having to hear from you.
Don't mind him.
He has no problem
having fun on his own.
I see.
Regarding the safe-deposit boxes
that the bank's VIP clients rent.
I believe items
worth hundreds of billions of won
such as diamonds, stocks and bonds
and top-secret documents are kept.
Were you keeping something important
in your safe-deposit box?
I wouldn't pay a fortune
to hide something unimportant.
We got a tip
that 500 billion won in cash
from KC Bank is going to be swapped
with counterfeit bills
while being transported.
I was looking into it
when I heard
your safe-deposit box was raided.
Until I find a connection
between the two incidents
we'll conduct a secret investigation.
I see.
I'm greatly relieved
that the NIS is on the case.
What did you say your name was?
- My name?
- Yes.
It's Cha Ki-tae.
Oh, Agent Cha's quick action.
I'll be sure to mention it
to your director.
You can do that.
I'll get going, then.
Sure.
I'll take one of these.
Oh, right.
Chairman, do you happen to know
someone called Jang Joong-hyuk?
He's head of the Violent Crimes Unit.
Do you know him?
Jang Joong-hyuk?
The name does sound familiar.
I meet so many people for work
and I have a lot on my mind.
I can't say for sure.
We're all like this at my age.
Sure.
How much of the information got out?
Joong-ki!
Yes?
Yes, Boss.
If you're thirsty
should you drink seawater or not?
You shouldn't.
It'll make you even more thirsty.
Right?
I didn't know that as a kid.
I couldn't help but drink.
Whether it were seawater or mud water
I had to drink it to feel better.
So
I drank it to my heart's content.
But you were right.
I actually got even thirstier
the more I drank.
That's what money is like.
The more you gain,
the thirstier you feel.
The more you crave.
Joong-ki.
That cash.
That's all mine.
Subtitles by Jennifer Jean Lim